

YOVIE ALFAGUISTUTA

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I am 23 years old and I am a web developer who have 2+ years of experience. Coding on React JS, Laravel and Go Language. I Already serve several clients to build web based applications. My greatest strength in technical terms is problem solving and logical thinking. I am also very enthusiastic and interested to use or learn new things.

SOFT SKILL

- Problem Solving
- · Logical Thinking
- Creativty
- Time Management
- Teamwork

TECH STACK

- React JS (Typescript)
- Laravel
- Golang



PROGRAMMING TOOLS

- Git
- Redux
- Docker & PM2
- Go Fiber
- Postman
- Jest
- Jira & Trello
- Linux
- PostgreeSql
- 2020

EDUCATION

2017 - 2021 Bachelor degree S1 Informatika (S.Kom)

at Universitas Teknokrat Indonesia,

GPA 3,45.

2015 - 2017 High school graduate from SMAN

5 Bandar Lampung, Science Major

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer Microdata Indonesia 2020 - 2022

Create, debug, test, analytze and modify more than 20+ apps from zero to produc-

tion

Web Developer Freelance 2020 - 2022

Develop variant application and system

for thesis

Internship Android Developer BAPPEDA (Intern)

Developing 2 Android Mobile Apps for Government activities within 2 months of

work

LANGUAGE

Indonesia

English









My Site http://yoviealfaguistuta.site



Address Pulau Sanama Street,

Bandar Lampung

